[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "If they do something, should America do anything, or does America keep out of this?", "question_tokens": ["If", "they", "do", "something", ",", "should", "America", "do", "anything", ",", "or", "does", "America", "keep", "out", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "We're not -- we're not at that point yet.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "not", "--", "we", "'re", "not", "at", "that", "point", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "Have you seen anything like that?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "seen", "anything", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Look.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Well, I think he will be getting a certain amount of heat from some people because there's no doubt the sanctions are having a big effect.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "he", "will", "be", "getting", "a", "certain", "amount", "of", "heat", "from", "some", "people", "because", "there", "'s", "no", "doubt", "the", "sanctions", "are", "having", "a", "big", "effect", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "Am I wrong to feel so pessimistic?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "wrong", "to", "feel", "so", "pessimistic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Well, it's understandable.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "understandable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Do you think it could still go either way?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "could", "still", "go", "either", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Well, you never know until the election actually happens.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "never", "know", "until", "the", "election", "actually", "happens", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "If you were going to be the incumbent come November the 7th, what kind of thing should the American administration, whoever it is, be looking to do quite quickly to try and stem this economic tide downward, which is going on all over the world?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "going", "to", "be", "the", "incumbent", "come", "November", "the", "7th", ",", "what", "kind", "of", "thing", "should", "the", "American", "administration", ",", "whoever", "it", "is", ",", "be", "looking", "to", "do", "quite", "quickly", "to", "try", "and", "stem", "this", "economic", "tide", "downward", ",", "which", "is", "going", "on", "all", "over", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 208, "question": "So you would have known?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "would", "have", "known", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Well, I don't -- I --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "Would you have known who wrote \"Rule Britannia\"?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "known", "who", "wrote", "``", "Rule", "Britannia", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "WP", "RB", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Clinton", "Bill Clinton"]}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "NN", "RB", "RBR", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Would that complete the peace project for you?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "that", "complete", "the", "peace", "project", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Well, the one thing I know is that in whatever country and whatever culture, whatever continent, whatever part of the world Bill Clinton was standing, everyone else better watch out, because he is the total master and he would -- he's just -- the thing that I always say about Bill Clinton is, the fascinating thing about him as a politician is that he's unbelievably smart and smart enough so that he doesn't come across as unbelievably smart.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "one", "thing", "I", "know", "is", "that", "in", "whatever", "country", "and", "whatever", "culture", ",", "whatever", "continent", ",", "whatever", "part", "of", "the", "world", "Bill", "Clinton", "was", "standing", ",", "everyone", "else", "better", "watch", "out", ",", "because", "he", "is", "the", "total", "master", "and", "he", "would", "--", "he", "'s", "just", "--", "the", "thing", "that", "I", "always", "say", "about", "Bill", "Clinton", "is", ",", "the", "fascinating", "thing", "about", "him", "as", "a", "politician", "is", "that", "he", "'s", "unbelievably", "smart", "and", "smart", "enough", "so", "that", "he", "does", "n't", "come", "across", "as", "unbelievably", "smart", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 250, "question": "Who would win?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 251, "answer": "Oh, there's no doubt about that, I'm afraid.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "doubt", "about", "that", ",", "I", "'m", "afraid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "This is -- this is a big problem for Mitt Romney, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "--", "this", "is", "a", "big", "problem", "for", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "I don't think it's quite as big a problem as you've made it out to be.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "'s", "quite", "as", "big", "a", "problem", "as", "you", "'ve", "made", "it", "out", "to", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Pretty impressive, Kate, isn't she?", "question_tokens": ["Pretty", "impressive", ",", "Kate", ",", "is", "n't", "she", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "My heavens, I take my hat off to her.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "heavens", ",", "I", "take", "my", "hat", "off", "to", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Do you worry about the pressure that you know she's going to be facing?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "worry", "about", "the", "pressure", "that", "you", "know", "she", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "facing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "I think she's able to cope with it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "she", "'s", "able", "to", "cope", "with", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Sarah Ferguson, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Sarah", "Ferguson", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "I'm doing very well, thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "very", "well", ",", "thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Ferguson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "Piers?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "It's been a very British show, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "a", "very", "British", "show", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "What advice do you give Kate for how to get through it and how to deal with it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "advice", "do", "you", "give", "Kate", "for", "how", "to", "get", "through", "it", "and", "how", "to", "deal", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Well, two things, really.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "two", "things", ",", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "How do you deal with that generally?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "deal", "with", "that", "generally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Well, I think -- I think it's very difficult because you are always -- you always worry so much.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "difficult", "because", "you", "are", "always", "--", "you", "always", "worry", "so", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "How is that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Yeah, I think that's very good.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "very", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "What are you trying to achieve with this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "trying", "to", "achieve", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Well, Piers, I think that education is the route out of poverty, because it gives the knowledge of survival.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "think", "that", "education", "is", "the", "route", "out", "of", "poverty", ",", "because", "it", "gives", "the", "knowledge", "of", "survival", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Ferguson"]}, "docId": "120927pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 543, "question": "And if you want to go and buy the book, I am not going to tell you the end of the tale, but you does \"Ballerina Rosie\" manage to do her pirouettes?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "you", "want", "to", "go", "and", "buy", "the", "book", ",", "I", "am", "not", "going", "to", "tell", "you", "the", "end", "of", "the", "tale", ",", "but", "you", "does", "``", "Ballerina", "Rosie", "''", "manage", "to", "do", "her", "pirouettes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Is there a touch of Sarah Ferguson in \"Ballerina Rosie?\"", "answer_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "touch", "of", "Sarah", "Ferguson", "in", "``", "Ballerina", "Rosie", "?", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]